

# **ANDREY LUSHCHIK**

# FRONT-END DEVELOPER

# **CONTACT INFO:**

- Minsk, Belarus
- andreylushchik56@gmail.com
- +375(29)778-51-26
- GitHub
- **in** Linkedin
- S Codewars

# **SKILLS:**

REACT REDUX TYPESCRIPT JAVASCRIPT HTML CSS

Node.js MySQL

UNIT TEST JEST

AXIOS RESTful API

MATERIAL UI TAILWIND

FIGMA GIT

#### **ABOUT ME**

Hi! I am a front end developer. I have experience creating a SPA using React, Redux, TypeScript, HTML and CSS. I am currently focused on improving my skills with the help of new technologies and tools. My hobbies are solving puzzles on Codewars, reading books about coding and watching tutorial videos. I keep polishing my English through apps, reading articles, documentation and watching TV shows. I like to learn something new.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Syberry Corporation

Minsk, Belarus Jun 2022 - Nov 2022

#### Maximum, Automobile Holding

St. Petersburg 2017-2019

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Creating 3 web applications (React/Java)
Working with documentation, server (Node.js),
database (MySQL)

Developed his teamwork skills by working closely with other developers

# MASTER CONSULTANT

Reception of customers for maintenance and repair of vehicles.

Conducting a dialog acceptance;

Advising clients, selling additional works and services;

Paperwork, work with custom orders, selection of spare parts;

Resolution of disputes and conflict situations

# **EDUCATION**

#### **TeachMeSkills**

Minsk, Belarus 2021-2022

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

The following technologies were used: TypeScript, React, Redux, Redux Thunk, Rest Api, Axios, Material UI, CSS, etc.

Designed and built SPA with functional and class components.

Supervised the creation of the Todo app on native JS.

Creating a CRUD app online store with authorization, modal windows, form checks, tests and menus.

Testing React and Redux components using Jest.

# **LANGUAGES**

RUSSIAN

**ENGLISH** 

PROFICIENCY(C2)
INTERMEDIATE(B1)